let savollar17 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "to appreciate",
        answer: "A. qadrlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. qadrlamoq",
            "B. mensimaslik",
            "C. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "D. past baholamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "available",
        answer: "B. mavjud",
        options: [
            "A. band",
            "B. mavjud",
            "C. cheklangan",
            "D. yopiq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "to beat",
        answer: "A. yengmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yengmoq",
            "B. yutqazmoq",
            "C. oldini olmoq",
            "D. zarar ko'rmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "bright",
        answer: "C. yorqin",
        options: [
            "A. qorong'i",
            "B. xira",
            "C. yorqin",
            "D. to'nk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to celebrate",
        answer: "D. nishonlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. motam tutmoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. unutmoq",
            "D. nishonlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to determine",
        answer: "B. tanlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. shubhalanmoq",
            "B. tanlamoq",
            "C. ikkilanmoq",
            "D. o'zgartirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to disappear",
        answer: "A. yo'qolmoq ketmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yo'qolmoq ketmoq",
            "B. paydo bo'lmoq",
            "C. qolmoq",
            "D. mavjud bo'lmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "else",
        answer: "C. boshqa",
        options: [
            "A. oldin",
            "B. shuning uchun",
            "C. boshqa",
            "D. deyarli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "fair",
        answer: "A. adolatli",
        options: [
            "A. adolatli",
            "B. adolatsiz",
            "C. noto'g'ri",
            "D. hiylakor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "to flow",
        answer: "D. oqmoq",
        options: [
            "A. turg'un",
            "B. to'xtamoq",
            "C. to'smoq",
            "D. oqmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "forward",
        answer: "B. oldinga",
        options: [
            "A. orqaga",
            "B. oldinga",
            "C. turg'un",
            "D. yon tomonga"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "hill",
        answer: "C. tepalik",
        options: [
            "A. vodiy",
            "B. tekislik",
            "C. tepalik",
            "D. tog'"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "level",
        answer: "A. daraja",
        options: [
            "A. daraja",
            "B. og'ish",
            "C. moyillik",
            "D. qiyshiq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "lone",
        answer: "D. yolg'iz",
        options: [
            "A. birga",
            "B. jamiyatda",
            "C. hamroh",
            "D. yolg'iz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "puddle",
        answer: "B. ko'lmak",
        options: [
            "A. daryo",
            "B. ko'lmak",
            "C. ko'l",
            "D. okean"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "response",
        answer: "C. javob",
        options: [
            "A. savol",
            "B. da'vo",
            "C. javob",
            "D. inkor"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "season",
        answer: "A. fasl",
        options: [
            "A. fasl",
            "B. oy",
            "C. hafta",
            "D. o'n yillik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "solution",
        answer: "B. yechim",
        options: [
            "A. muammo",
            "B. yechim",
            "C. savol",
            "D. vazifa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to waste",
        answer: "C. isrof qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tejamoq",
            "B. foydalamoq",
            "C. isrof qilmoq",
            "D. saqlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "whether",
        answer: "A. yoki",
        options: [
            "A. yoki",
            "B. va",
            "C. yoki",
            "D. chunki"
        ]
    }
];
